Guide to the WDBS Collection, 1949 - 1983 UA.31.12.0005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiotapes, 1956-1973, undated; 5
  - Allen Building Takeover, 1969 February 10-1969 March 12; 3
    - Dick Gregory Visit, Allen Building Takeover: Tape #6, 1969 February 10, 1969 February 17 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0033)
      1. Afro Allen Bldg Takeover wrap-up report; Chris Santy-correspondent February 17, 1969; 2. Report by Chris Santy (David Christy) on visit of Dick Gregory to Duke campus February 10, 1969
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #7, 1969 February 13-1969 February 16 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0034)
      Afro Take Over of Allen Bldg. Reports by Chris Santy (alias David Christy)
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #8, 1969 February 15 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0035)
      Rally at Dr. Knight's house after Afro-Am takeover of Allen Building. Recorded by Duke Univ. Information Services
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #9, 1969 February 15, 1970 January 21 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0036)
      1. Actualities for Page Convocation, 12:30 p.m., February 15, 1969; 2. Tom Fine spot hospital workers sit-in. Statement by Doctor who allegedly struck black hospital worker, January 21, 1970; 3. Robert Chapman spot on sit-in by workers affiliated with Local 1199D at Duke hospital arrested for trespassing after nursing office sit-in, January 1970
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #10, 1969 February 15 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0037)
      Part I: Convocation-Introduction of president of Afro-Ams at Page. Recorded following Afro take-over of Allen Building.
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #11, 1969 February 15 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0038)
      Part III: Convocation called by students following Afro take-over of Allen Bldg.; Contents:Howard Fuller (part II); Tom Rainey of History Dept.; Dean Griffith (part I)
    - Convocation at Page following Allen Bldg. takeover: Tape #12, 1969 February 15 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0039)
    - Convocation at Page Auditorium, part 2: Tape #13, 1969 February 15 (Box 5, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0040)
    - WDBS News: Tape #14, 1969 February-1969 March (Box 6, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0041)
      1. Preface by Dr. Knight aired February 15, 1969 7pm; 2. Don Baumgardner, March 10, 1969; 3. Apollo 9 liftoff by ABC radio; 4. President Knight resignation, March 27, 1969, Baumgardner and Braswell; 5. President Knight at his home during the February 1969 crisis
    - Dr. Knight's Speech: Tape #15, 1969 February 16 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0042)
    - Page Meetings, 2:30 p.m., part 1: Tape #16, 1969 February 16 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0043)
    - Page Meetings, 2:30 p.m., part 3: Tape #17, 1969 February 16 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0044)
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #18, 1969 March 12 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0045)
      Ashmore statement during February 69 crisis; Report on crisis on campus, midnite, February 12, 1969; Dean Griffith, March 12, 1969; Frank L. Ashmore, March 12, 1969
    - Allen Building Crisis: Tape #19, 1969 February (Box 6, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0046)
      Wrap-up of Afro-Allen events, February 13- 16, 1969
    - Fuller and Afros at Baldwin [Howard Fuller and African-American Students at Baldwin Auditorium], part 1, 1969 March 5 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0047)
    - Fuller and Afros at Baldwin [Howard Fuller and African-American Students at Baldwin Auditorium], part 2, 1969 March 5 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0048)
    - Actualities Downtown, 1969 March 11 (Box 6, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0049)
    - Racial Unrest in Durham, 1969 March (Box 6, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0050)
  - Musical performances, 1956-1968, undated; 4
    - Fleischer: Organ Recital, 1956 February 5 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0106)
    - Sound Board: Master #1, 1956 Dec. 2 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0107)
    - Sound Board: Master #2, 1966 Dec. 2 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0108)
    - Duke Concert Band, part 1, 1967 April 14 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0109)
    - Duke Concert Band, part 2, 1967 April 14 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0110)
    - Senior Recital, part 1, 1967 April 17 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0111)
    - Senior Recital, part 2, 1967 April 17 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0112)
    - Men's Glee Club: Baldwin Auditorium, Session 2, 1967 April (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0113)
    - Men's Glee Club: Baldwin Auditorium, Session 3, 1967 April (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0114)
    - Men's Glee Club: Baldwin Auditorium, Session 4, 1967 April (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0115)
    - Duke Symphony Student Soloists, 1967 May 12 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0116)
    - Duke Symphony Student Soloists, 1967 May 12 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0117)
    - Duke Concert Band, 1967 Dec. 8 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0118)
    - Women's and Men's Glee Club, 1968 April 18 (Box 7, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0120)
    - Chapel Choir, 1968 March 17; 10 inch reel (Box 8, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0119)
    - Introduction Philharmonic Orchestra: Allan Bone, undated; 10 inch reel (Box 8, Audio-reel UA31120005-RR-0121)